<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IDE_Fantasy glove documentation</title>
    <link>https://loopynid.github.io/ideFantasyDoc/</link>
    <description>Recent content on IDE_Fantasy glove documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 16:46:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://loopynid.github.io/ideFantasyDoc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Manual of Magnetic Dance glove</title>
      <link>https://loopynid.github.io/ideFantasyDoc/posts/manual-of-magnetic-dance-glove/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 16:46:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loopynid.github.io/ideFantasyDoc/posts/manual-of-magnetic-dance-glove/</guid>
      <description>General Overview: The glove sets up a wifi network. The computer running supercollider connects to this network and recieves the sensor data from the glove. In parallel it connects to a second wifi network which provides internet access.
Steps:
 connect the computer running supercollider to the &amp;ldquo;glove network&amp;rdquo; access internet via the glove  Connect to &amp;ldquo;glove network&amp;rdquo; Firstly connect the glove to power. After 3-4 minutes your computer should de- tect a wifi network named MD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Glove assembly</title>
      <link>https://loopynid.github.io/ideFantasyDoc/posts/glove-assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 16:46:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loopynid.github.io/ideFantasyDoc/posts/glove-assembly/</guid>
      <description>Components needed  raspberry pi zero w (rpi zero w is preferred because of size, but this setup is also tested on rpi 3 and rpi 3+) sd card at least 2gb in size the magnetic dance rasbian image an i2c sensor in this case a BNO055 4x patch cables  Assembly Installing rasbian image to sd card The downloaded image will be in .zip format. All information needed for this step can be found here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rasbian image setup</title>
      <link>https://loopynid.github.io/ideFantasyDoc/posts/rasbian-image-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 16:47:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loopynid.github.io/ideFantasyDoc/posts/rasbian-image-setup/</guid>
      <description>The image used in this project is based on the rasbian stretch lite Version: November 2018.
Wifi functionality For the purpose of this project we need to connect to a &amp;ldquo;parent&amp;rdquo; network and setup a &amp;ldquo;child&amp;rdquo; network. To achieve this we will need hostapd, dnsmasq, iptables-persistent and some configuration because we want to use the built in wifi as an client to a network (&amp;ldquo;parent&amp;rdquo; network) and an access point for a second network (&amp;ldquo;child&amp;rdquo; network) at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://loopynid.github.io/ideFantasyDoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://loopynid.github.io/ideFantasyDoc/</guid>
      <description>IDE_Fantasy IDE Fantasy: Telematic Dance for 3 Performers with IMU sensors, SuperCollider and Godot Gaming Engine
The whole IDE Fantasy performance is combines Supercollider for audio production, the Godot game engine for graphics and Hamachi vpn + osc to achieve the telematic nature of the piece.
This is the technical implementation of the the sensor glove the dancers wear in the performance.
The glove uses the Raspberry pi zero w because of its open source and connectivity benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>